(Sheldon:)...is secreting the pheromones
associated with ovulation.
(Sheldon:)Which brings me back to my question.
Where are you in...?
(Sheldon:)Clearly, I'm 14 days too early.
(Leonard:)All I'm saying is,
if they can cure yellow fever and malaria...
(Leonard:)...why can't they do something
about lactose intolerance?
Leonard, you're gonna have to let this go.
(Steph:)You had a little cheese dip, you farted.
I thought it was cute.
(Sheldon:)Oh, hi, Stephanie.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
- Want some more wine?
- Yeah.
(Steph:)I mean,
I assume I'm not driving anywhere tonight.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[SHELDON GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)I have a craving for white asparagus that,
apparently, is destined to go unsatisfied.
[GRUNTS]